Yamanaka Komura, Yamanashi Prefecture
In this place where the battle of Yamanaka between Takeda Nobuta and others and Hojo Gojushima once took place
A new battle was about to begin again.
Shingei Mochi
If you eat this, what will you use it for?
This is a version of the maiden temple war training dialect.
We'll use the local version.
If you don't mind if I leave it here...
I'm glad we're doing this.
But the staff will be managed.
If you put the shingemochi in the top of this...
When to use it, though.
But you know what I was just talking about...
Shinge mochi, they'll go bad if you leave them there
You should eat it and just look at the package often
You might as well eat it
Are your eyes sunburned? Your eyes are red.
I wonder what's inside.
You want to open it?
Wait a minute.
It doesn't really mean anything inside.
It's fixed in place.
It's hard.
Do you need a step ladder?
I don't know if it's safe to have them in there.
If it's in one of these.
I'll just pack something else.
I'll need a shaped cardboard box.
You know, shaped cardboard boxes.
When you get something like this...
Here? But there's no sign of the new artisans?
It's nighttime. I wonder if they're still here.
Here, one week.
I'll give you a week.
I don't care. It's nighttime.
If you stand up at night, you won't get so much of this...It's not so hot when you stand up at night.
It's not so hot, is it?
It's not so hot when you sing from the very first song.
Next time
I bought it for the production, at first.
So I don't care what's in it.
I've already finished making it now.
If there is a rody, that is important.
Because even the set is only the surface.
On the stage.
Surely.
That's right, that's right!
If you look at the back, it's like a tree.
That's right.
You can't see the back.
I can't see it.
Go ahead and put it in already.
I've already put it in.
I already put it in the back corner.
Art book
This is
Peach's
Oh! The one with the wrappings.
Peaches wrapped in
The fruit
It's white!
It's white! It's a peach's feeling.
This one, too.
You're smiling back there.
Yeah, totally.
She's making a smile.
It's amazing, isn't it?
My smile is better.
It's so tight.
It's like...
Like a tourist.Like a tourist visitor.
Something like, you know, a hot spot.
I'm a tourist attraction.
Oh, my God, you have ripped abs.
You got abs? Wow!
Daikoku's been on fire lately.
Including his solo birthday the other day.
I've saved a lot of pictures of your abs.
Even when I'm taking this video now, there's still a little bit of a line.
I'm so happy!
I'm always explaining to my trainer.
This is what it looks like now.
Pictures from the live show.
Which picture, what's wrong with it?
Nao uploaded Yuzuki's background
Yuzuki's background to Slez.
She's thinking of words!
Oh, that's great, but...
Oh my God, that's too much!
I'll put it in Spark.
He really seems to have gotten excited.
What shall we call it?
Matchmaking, that maiden's matchmaking...
Go for it!
Go for it
Losing girl
See, I can hear you.
Then you'll understand.
Maybe I'll recognize you.
I'm like, "Wow, that's a Soulette's!
You're on.
Oh, my God, you're gonna do it!
I'll get down!
It's the Slet's part!
It's the comedy part.It's the part of the big comedy.
I'm going to post this on my instagram and on my threads.
I have to do it.
I have to do it!
So, I'm going to eat a Shingenmochi.
Place the Shingenmochi on the tatami mats.
It's so heavy!
Looks delicious!
Spark!
Spark the shingenmochi first!
Bon appétit!
How is it?
Yum!
Delicious!
So delicious!
So soft!
Taste the same?
I'm glad I trusted you.
It's so hard to open this, but I can't.
What song is this?
A memory of your hometown.
Wait, wait, wait. He's suddenly immersed in his hometown.
What do you mean?
I started the Ginza story.
The Shinbara script.
Oh, there's a commercial? Shinbara letters.
I'm sure there is.
I didn't know that.
It was like our frog manjuu.
Because it's Kikagaya's.
You mean it's a Kikkyo-ya song?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, I remember now.
Also, there is a famous commercial for a local dry-cleaning company called Dry Cleaning Shimura.
We are Aichi Small ElevatorWe are Aichi Small Elevator
Aichi Small Elevator
You know the black and white, green tea, sweet coffee, yuzu, cherry blossom?
I don't know it.
The Willow.
The Willow?
Yes.
Willow's.
What's with the frog buns?
One mountain to another, one pond to another
with a big smile and big eyes
Frog manju done!
Bon appétit!
Frog buns with a blue top
What did you say first?
I wish you would have waited a little longer.
I wanted to eat it with you.
Okay, you want a second one?
No, thanks.
Sure.
Here you go.
Bon appétit.
Bravo.
But what's up with the level?
Maybe because it's hot, the rice cake has softened.
It's so delicious.
So soft and delicious.
Did you get a reaction?
I think everyone's a little surprised.
I'm sure they are.
It's almost like Mongolian wrestling.
What do you mean?
It's delicious.
I don't know.something
It's hot!
Oh, man!
And the Mongols.
The two of you came back.
We talked about Mr. Oguro's back all the way through the video.
Amazing, isn't it?
Look at that.
Look at this.
There were two posts.
The first one.
What? Oh, my God.
The second one.
I kind of gave him the scent.
See? Can you hear me? There you go.
But you know, I wasn't expecting to see so many available.
No, no, no. I just bought it.
I didn't think so.
You were pretty surprised.
I was surprised when I went to the convenience store.
That's when I noticed.
You were riding in this without your jacket?
Yeah.
What do you mean, "almost a Mongolian duckling"?
I got a comment that it's almost a Mongolian gerbil.
Oh, my God, that's what the thumbnail of the video is going to look like.
Let's look up "Mongolian duckling" for a moment.
I wonder if Mongolian Zumo means they want us to go along with Mongolian Zumo?
I think that's what it means, right? Mongolian?
But it's not.
Please subscribe to our channel.